Do you like this dress,madam?
女士,您喜欢这件衣服吗?
I like the colour very much.
我很喜欢这颜色.
It's a lovely dress, but it's too small for me.
这是件漂亮的衣服,可是对我来说太小了.
What about this one? It's a lovely dress.
这件怎么样?这是件漂亮的衣服.
It's very smart.
它很时髦.
Short skirts are in fashion now.
短裙现在很流行.
Would you like to try it?
您要试一试吗?
All right.
好吧.
I'm afraid this green dress is too small for me as well.
恐怕这件绿色的我穿着也太小了.
It's smaller than the blue one.
它比那件蓝色的还要小.
I don't like the colour either.
我也不喜欢这种颜色.
It doesn't suit me at all.
它完全不适合我.
I think the blue dress is prettier.
我认为那件蓝色的更漂亮些.
Could you show me another blue dress?
您能再给我看一件蓝色的吗?
I want a dress like that one, but it must be my size.
我想要一件和那件一样的,但必须是我的尺寸.
I'm afraid I haven't got a larger dress.
恐怕没有更大的了.
This is the largest dress in the shop.
这是店里最大的一件.